（影山 律(かげやま　りつ)）
うわあ 気持ちいい！
Wow!
It feels so good!
Hey, do you think
I'll be able to do this, too?
ねえ 僕にも
できるようになるかな？
Yeah.
（モブ）
うん！
だって 律は僕の弟だもん！
Of course you will. You're my little brother.
（律）
はっ
ハア～
ハア…
あっ
くっ
ふっ！ はっ！
ふぉ！ ぐっ！
くっ くっ くっ うう ううう…
～
Mob Psycho
Discord
~To Become One~
Spirits and Such Consultation Office
We will now begin the seance.
（霊幻新隆(れいげんあらたか)）
それでは これより
降霊の儀を執り行います
Client: Hitoshi
（霊幻）
ああっ！ ハア…
I-Is that you, Dad?
（ヒトシ）
お… おやじなのか？
Do you know who I am?
（ヒトシ）
この俺が分かるか？
おお？ おお… ヒトシよ
Oh, Hitoshi...
まさか再び お前の顔が
見られる日が来ようとは…
I never thought the day would come
when I got to see your face again...
Dad...
おやじ
When did you learn to speak Japanese so well?
（ヒトシ）
いつの間に そんな 日本語
しゃべれるようになったんだ？
はい！ 一旦 ログアウトしま～す
Okay, logging out for a sec.
Huh?
えっ？
Sorry, I'm not getting a very good signal.
（霊幻）
すみませんね　何か電波 悪くて
Were you satisfied?
満足しましたか？
No!
そんな！
もう１回 呼んでくださいよ！
Please call him back!
Hey, please calm down.
（霊幻）
ちょっ 落ち着いてください！
神経 使うんですよ 降霊は
Seances take a lot of concentration.
By the way, where is your father from?
ところで あなたのお父さんって
出身どこなの？
New Jersey in America.
America(アメリカ) の New Jersey(ニュージャージー)州です
All foreign languages will be
auto-translated into Japanese.
（霊幻）
外国語は全て自動翻訳されます
ええっ？
これは霊の言語周波数を
あれする高等技術ですが
This is an advanced technique
that does something-or-other
to the wavelength of the spirit's languages,
but there will not be an additional fee.
追加料金は発生しません！
That's amazing! But I'm okay with English.
すっごい！
でも 僕は英語でもＯＫです！
Now, then...
（霊幻）
それでは
Oh, Hitoshi! How have you been?
オウ ヒト～シ
元気にしてマ～スカ？
日本語だ　まあ いいか
It's Japanese... Well, whatever.
Dad, do you remember?
おやじ 覚えてるか？
Remember how we used to
play ball when I was a kid?
小さいころ ball(ボール)で遊んでてさ
And we did that one thing that
was popular on TV back then?
一緒に やったよな？
当時 はやってた television(テレビ) の…
久しぶりに見せてくれよ！
Show it to me one more time!
（ヒトシ）
おやじ？
Dad?
Huh? What was that...
えっ 今の動きは？
"Cheeseburger Tornado,"
the main character's special move
当時 はやっていたドラマ
「ジャンクフード戦士 マイケル」
の主人公の奥義
in "Junk Food Fighter Michael,"
the super popular show at the time.
“チーズバーガートルネード”
だが？
Huh? What the heck?
（ヒトシ）
は？ 何？ それ
Anyway, Hitoshi...
それよりもだ ヒト～シよ
Cut to the chase and tell me what you want.
用件をタント～チョクニュ～に
言いなさい
おやじ…
Dad...
チッ！ ご機嫌取りを見破られちゃ
しょうがねえ
If being cordial won't work, then screw it!
Yo, you shitty old man!
よお クソじじい！
Tell me the password to the hidden safe!
I know there's a fortune in there!
隠し金庫の password(パスワード)
教えやがれ！
大金があるはずだ～
Um, I think the password was my birthday...
えっと パスワードは
俺の誕生日トカ ダッタヨウナ…
Don't give me that crap!
It's thirteen letters of the alphabet!
とぼけるな！
alphabet(アルファベット) 13文字だろうが！
With that money,
I'll chill for the rest of my life!
俺は その金で
一生 遊んで暮らすんだよ
オウ！ 思い出しマ～シタ
Oh, now I remember!
The password is...
パスワードは…
"GETAJOBYOUBUM"!
“HATARAKINASAI(ハタラキナサイ)”ダ～！
Cheeseburger Tornado
This is one of Reigen's special moves,
where he uses his whole body like a spring
（ナレーション）
全身のバネを使い
強烈な回転の
かかった拳を
and smashes his fist into his opponent's
face with a powerful spin.
相手の顔面にたたき込む
霊幻の必殺技である
（ヒトシ）
うぐっ
しまった！
依頼人の意識がログアウトした
Crap! The client's consciousness logged out!
Reception
Limited Time Offer
Get 3 evil spirit
exorcisms for the
price of 2!
Did he pass out?
（モブ）
気絶したんですか？ この人
Yeah... But, well, it was self-defense.
（霊幻）
ああ
けど まあ 正当防衛だ
正当防衛？
Self-defense...
What? You look a bit pale.
（霊幻）
何だ？ 顔色 悪いぞ？
If it's self-defense,
（モブ）
正当防衛だったら
相手の髪の毛を刈り取って
is it okay to shave off someone's hair,
rip off their clothes,
服をはぎ取って
プライド へし折って
Teru
destroy their pride,
make them lose their friends,
友達なくさせて
and destroy the school they go to?
通ってる学校を破壊しても
いいんですかね？
How can you do that much in self-defense?
（霊幻）
どうやったら
正当防衛で そこまでできるの？
僕の超能力は—
There are times when my psychic powers
go out of control...
たまに勝手に
動きだすんです
And it happens when I'm unconscious, to boot.
それも
僕の意識がないときに
I don't want these powers anymore.
（モブ）
こんな“力”
もう持っていたくない
If nothing else, they're of use to me.
少なくとも 俺の役には立ってる
And it's not just me.
（霊幻）
俺だけじゃない
Think of all of the clients
you helped with those powers.
事実 何人もの依頼人が
お前のおかげで救われただろ？
Don't just focus on the negatives.
マイナス面ばかり見るな
It's all about how you use knives, remember?
刃物は使いようだろうが！ な？
自分を殺すな
Don't suppress yourself.
You're the one who holds the keys
to maximizing your potential.
お前を生かせるのは
お前しかいないんだ
信用しろ
Trust me.
You'll be fine.
（霊幻）
お前は大丈夫だ
（モブ）
フウ…
Huh?
（山崎(やまざき)）
えっ？ “裏番システム”っすか？
The shadow leader system?
（鬼瓦天牙(おにがわらてんが)）
そうだ
Yeah.
I completely lost to that
shadow leader named Hanazawa,
（鬼瓦）
俺は花沢って裏番に
こてんぱんに負けたが
そいつに勝った男が
この塩(しお)中には いる
but the guy who beat him
is from Salt Middle School.
Someone that strong?
（鳥海(とりうみ)）
そんな強(つえ)えヤツが？
ああ これからは
そいつに裏番になってもらう
Yeah. We're gonna have him
be our shadow leader.
（米里(めざと)イチ）
モブ君でしょ？
黒酢(くろず)中の怪奇現象 起こしたの
You're the one who caused the supernatural
incident at Black Vinegar Middle, right?
U-Um...
えっ？ えっと…
You're basically the only person
who could do that.
（米里）
あんなことできるの
モブ君しかいないもんね
Oh, but according to the rumors...
でも ウワサによると
There's a kid at Black Vinegar Middle
who easily throws people around, too.
（米里）
黒酢中にも軽々と人を
吹き飛ばす子がいるんだって！
Maybe he's an esper just like you...
もしかして その彼も
超能力者だったりして！
And then you two met at Black
Vinegar Middle School, and fought.
そんで ２人は
黒酢中で出会って対決した
An esper battle!
That's what happened, right?
超能力対決したんでしょ？
Twitch, twitch.
（暗田(くらた)トメ）
ピクピク
You don't want to talk about it?
（米里）
話したくない？
（モブ）
うん
That's enough for today, then.
（米里）
じゃあ 今日はいいわ
でも いつか
必ず話を聞かせてもらうわよ！
But someday, you're definitely
going to tell me all about it.
ハア…
Mob-kun?!
モブ君！
You mean that wasn't the work of aliens?
（暗田）
あれって
宇宙人の仕業じゃなかったの？
And that aside, there are
espers other than yourself?
ていうか それより モブ君以外にも
超能力者っているの？
いました
Yes...
ムフフフフ…
You can find them, right?
（暗田）
探せるのね？
えっ 今まで会ったの
１人だけですよ？
Huh? I've only met one other in my life.
That's strange. What about your master?
（暗田）
おかしいわね　あんたの師匠は？
あっ…
Ah...
Come to think of it, I don't
sense anything from my master.
そういえば
師匠からは何も感じないや
But that's because his powers
are spiritual, not psychic.
師匠は超能力者じゃなくて
Psychic
霊能力者だから
Spiritual
What kind of rule is that?
（暗田）
何？ そのルール
まあ いいわ
Well, whatever.
Let's go on a date after this.
（暗田）このあと デートしましょ
（モブ）えっ！
Huh?
We're going to find other
telepathic people together!
一緒に探すのよ！
テレパシー使いを
And then take our first step toward
connecting with outer space!
そして 宇宙とつながる第一歩を
踏み出すの！
But I'm not in the Telepathy Club.
僕 脳感電波部じゃないんですけど
Black Vinegar Middle School's shadow leader?
（郷田武蔵(ごうだむさし)）
黒酢中の裏番長？
俺は負けたぞ
あの男 ナイス筋肉であった
I lost to him.
That guy had some nice muscles.
Th-Then who beat him?
じゃ 誰が倒したんだ？
肉改部の誰かだろ？
It was someone from your club, right?
He's a gentleman who
usually dislikes violence.
“彼”は
本来 暴力が嫌いな紳士なんだ
Do not involve him in this. Begone.
“彼”を巻き込むな！ 去れ！
Tch. Damn that Musashi...
チッ！ 武蔵の野郎
うん？
Hey.
（鬼瓦）おい
（モブ）うわっ あ… はい
Huh? Y-Yes?
You were picked on by the guys from Black
Vinegar Middle School last week, weren't you?
お前 先週 黒酢中のヤツらに
絡まれただろ？
あれ 全部 俺のせいだ
悪かったな
That was all my fault. Sorry about that.
Huh? What do you...
えっ？ どういう…
Don't sweat the small stuff!
細けえことは いいんだよ！
悪いな 影山
Sorry, Kageyama.
Tenga-san's an idiot,
so he can't explain things proper—
天牙さん バカだから
ちゃんと説明でき…
（鬼瓦）
うっせ～！
Shut up!
You asshole!
バカ野郎が！
I'm talking to him. Stay out of it!
俺は こいつと話してんだよ
黙ってろ～！
Well, then...
（徳川(とくがわ)）
それでは今月 生徒会で行う
校内運動は以上とする
That will be all of the student council's
activities for this month.
よろしいですね？ 神室(かむろ)会長
Is that all right, President Kamuro?
Well...
（神室真司(かむろしんじ)）
そうだねえ
Salt Middle School
Student Council President:
Kamuro
Shinji
悪くはないんだけど
It's not bad, but we need
something with more impact.
もうひとつインパクトに
欠けるような
ねえ？ １年生 影山君
Don't you think so,
first-year, Kageyama-kun?
えっ…
全国模試でも上位に入る
君の意見が聞きたい
You rank as one of the smartest in the nation,
so I want to hear your opinion.
Right... In our school,
（律）
はい
校内には いわゆる“不良”と
呼ばれる生徒が存在します
there are students known as delinquents.
Pending
Box
彼らに対して
生徒会で注意などができれば
If the student council could reprimand them,
平和な学園作りが
できるのではないかと…
I think we'd be able to
create a peaceful school.
I see... a peaceful school, eh?
なるほど 校内の平和か
Disciplining Delinquents
That's great. Let's do that.
いいじゃない　採用
I have to make it a comfortable
environment for my brother...
（律）
兄さんが生きやすい環境に
しなければ
Kageyama-kun?
（男）
影山君？
Thank goodness. I guess there was a
point in waiting around after all.
よかった
待ち伏せしたかいがあったよ
Awakening Lab
Mitsuura Kenji
Here are my credentials.
私は こういう者です
Awakening Lab?
（律）
覚醒(かくせい)ラボ？
What do you think, Kageyama-kun?
（密裏賢治(みつうらけんじ)）
どうかな？ 影山君
Why not try to amplify your psychic powers
at my research facility?
（密裏）
君の超能力 私の研究施設で
もっと増幅させてみないかい？
He's got me confused with Nii-san.
（律）
僕を兄さんと勘違いしている
Ah, Tome-san. That person—
あっ トメさん あの人…
なに？ 超能力者？
What? Is he an esper?!
No, I just thought he had
a very unique hairstyle.
（モブ）
いや あの人
すごい髪形してるなと思って
あら ホント
Oh, you're right.
遊んでんじゃねえぞ
Stop fooling around!
I'm being serious.
（モブ）
いや 真面目にやってますよ
Awakening Lab
Mitsuura Kenji
Oh, it's you, Kageyama.
（徳川）
何だ 影山か
ああ 徳川副会長
Ah, Vice President Tokugawa.
Loitering, huh?
（徳川）
道草か
I guess even people like you
feel like doing that at times.
君のようなタイプでも
そういう気持ちになるんだな
Like me? I'm just a normal middle school
student you can find anywhere.
タイプ？
どこにでもいる中学生だと
思うのですが
Totally simple and normal.
至って素朴で普通の…
至って素朴で普通の中学生など
地球上のどこを探してもいない
You won't find a totally simple and normal
middle schooler anywhere on this planet.
だが どういうわけか
But, for whatever reason, you want to
be one and are trying to act the part.
君は そうなりたくて
演じている節がある
I'm not sure if I understand
what you're saying.
言ってる意味が
よく分からないですね
Despite having abilities that always
make you the center of attention,
（徳川）
君は嫌でも目立ってしまうほど
優秀でありながら
you try to play the minor role
and let others have the spotlight.
注目を他人に譲り
端役を選びたがるということだ
Don't try to act like your brother.
兄のマネは よせ
（律）
あ…
Captain! Kageyama-kun is...
くっ…
（佐川(さがわ)）
部長 影山君が！
I'm fine...
I think you're starting to
build up some stamina!
ぶへ… 大丈夫です！
（郷田）
おう！ スタミナ
ついてきたんじゃないか？
Progress Towards
Mob's Explosion
Progress Toward Mob's Explosion: 4%
Awakening Lab?
（律）
覚醒ラボ
This place?
ここが？
どう見ても ただのマンション…
This is clearly just a normal
apartment complex—
Fortress
Seasoning
Kageyama-kun!
影山く～ん！
You came!
来てくれたのか～！
研究施設なんてない！
デマだったんですね？
There's no research facility here.
You lied to me.
Now, now, just come in.
（密裏）
まあまあ 入って 入って
Welcome...
ようこそ
to the Awakening Lab!
覚醒ラボへ！
What is this place?
（律）
何だ？ ここは
I bought an apartment complex
and remodeled it.
（密裏）
マンションを買い取って
改造したんだよ
I've hired the front runners in
neural science and engineering,
脳科学やら 神経工学の有識者を
雇って研究してるのさ
and we do research here.
この上の階に
超能力者の子供たちがいる
The esper kids are on the floor above us.
いるんですか？
They are?
フッ いるよ 君以外にもね
Yeah, there are other people just like you.
いた
There...
（暗田）
うん？ 変な髪形の人？
Another guy with a weird haircut?
That's an adult esper.
（モブ）
大人の超能力者だ
What is this feeling? It's kind of sickening.
何だろう？ この感じ
何か 気持ち悪いな
ごめん トメさん 見間違いでした
Sorry, Tome-san. I was wrong.
モブ君 見て！
Look, Mob-kun! Isn't that
hairstyle super weird?
あの髪形 すごい変じゃない？
Allow me to introduce them.
（密裏）
それでは 紹介しよう
Real espers that the Mitsuura Group
worked hard to bring together!
彼らは密裏グループの総力を挙げて
結集させた—
本物の超能力者たちだ
First is Hoshino Takeshi-kun.
Hoshino
Takeshi
まずは 星野武史(ほしの　たけし)君！
（武史）
ふん くっ ふっ！
くうう… ふん… ぐうう…
全開だっしゃあ～！
I'm going all out!
He has psychokinetic powers!
念動力使い
Is that supposed to be amazing?
（律）
これ すごいのか？
（密裏）
続いて 黒崎(くろさき) 麗(れい)さん
Kurosaki
Rei
Next, we have Kurosaki Rei-san.
Her powers of clairvoyance allow her
to pick the one correct card out of ten!
（密裏）
10枚のカードから１枚を当てる
超直感力の持ち主
Her efficiency rate is 62%!
その確率 62パーセント
Yay! I was right again!
（麗）
わ～い また当たった！
That's it?
（律）
その程度なのか？
Next, we have Asahi Go-kun.
Asahi
Go
（密裏）
お次は 朝日(あさひ) 豪(ごう)君
（豪）
見な パイロキネシス
Behold, my pyrokinesis!
Ignite!
着火！
あれ？
Huh?
ん… 着火！ 着火！
Ignite! Ignite!
ちゃ… ついた！
Ig—There we go! Oh, it went out.
あっ 消えた
He uses pyrokinesis.
発火能力使い
And is less useful than a 100-yen lighter...
（律）
100円ライター以下
（密裏）
白鳥(しらとり)兄弟
The Shiratori brothers:
Daichi-kun and Kaito-kun.
Shiratori
Daichi
Kaito
大地(だいち)君 アンド 海斗(かいと)君
They're telepaths who can communicate
with each other, even when they're apart.
（密裏）
離れていても
２人の間で意思疎通ができる
テレパシー使い
And less useful than email.
（律）
メール以下
This is Kageyama Shigeo-kun. Be nice to him.
（密裏）
こちら 影山茂夫(しげお)君だ
仲良くしてやってくれ
Nice to meet you.
（武史）
よろしく
（麗）
よろしくね
Nice to meet you.
Did Mitsuura-san do something to all of you?
みんな 密裏さんに何かされた？
Well, that's rather rude.
そんな 人聞きの悪い！
Don't worry. That old man is just
fascinated with psychic powers.
（武史）
大丈夫だよ
そのおっさん
ただ超能力に憧れてるだけだから
（律）
えっ？
Huh?
私はね
とある資産家の息子なんだが
I'm the son of a very wealthy family,
but I'm not anyone special.
何者でもない
I don't believe in doing anything to make
advancements in society or science.
社会や科学の発展のためなんて
気持ちは さらさらない
I just want to become an esper myself.
私自身が超能力者になりたいんだ
So I made a research facility. That's all!
だから 研究施設を作った
それだけ！
This is a childish pipe dream,
（律）
子供じみた絵空事だけど
実現できるんだったら 興味はある
but if he's able to make that
happen, I'd be interested.
I always wanted to rise to my standards.
ずっと基本に立つことが目標だった
Oh, Shinji. You're finally home?
（神室の母）
あら 真司 やっと帰ったの？
Kamuro
（母）
また生徒会？
お遊びも ほどほどにしなさいね
Student council again? Make sure
you don't fool around too much.
うう…
Nii-san was the student
council president, too.
兄さんだって
生徒会長やってたじゃないか
（母）
でも 卓哉(たくや)は—
But Takuya was also good in his studies.
勉強ができたじゃないの
Exactly. I'm embarrassed, Shinji.
（神室卓哉）
まったくだ
俺は恥ずかしいぞ 真司
You haven't even hit a
standardized score of 70 yet?
（卓哉）
まだ 偏差値70
いってないんだってな
Are you really my younger brother?
ホントに俺の弟かよ？
You suck at violin, drawing,
calligraphy, and have no talent,
バイオリンも絵画も書道もダメで
才能ないから
生徒会長になったんだろ？
so you became the student
council president, right?
Then, you should have time to study.
だったら 勉強する時間あるだろ？
How much are you going to
disappoint Mom and Dad?
どこまで 父さんや母さんを
失望させるんだ？ え？
Elites like—
ハア…
（モブ）
あ～ん
Ah.
あ…
Ugh, you need to really
fix that habit of yours.
（モブの母）
もう その癖
いいかげんに直しなさいよ
But it just bends on its own.
（モブ）
だって 勝手に曲がっちゃうんだ
（モブの父）
ハハハハ おならかって～の！
What is it, a fart?
Oh, stop that! We're eating dinner!
（母）
あなた！ 食事中に下品よ
Shige, you need to be more like Ritsu.
（母）
茂 少しは律を見習いなさい！
Yeah.
（モブ）
そうだね
Ritsu is much more talented than I am
and doesn't do anything weird.
律は僕より器用だし
変なことしないし
（鳥のさえずり）
おはよう 影山君
Good morning, Kageyama-kun.
どうしたんですか？ 会長
こんな朝早くに呼び出しなんて
What's wrong, President?
Why did you call me here so early?
This is a girl's recorder bag.
（神室）
これは女子のリコーダー袋だね
中には何が入ってると思う？
What do you think is inside?
A girl's recorder.
（律）
女子のリコーダーですね
Correct...
正解
会長？
President?
It's long, so let's just take this off.
（神室）
長いから 外しちゃおう
What have you been doing, President?
（律）
さっきから
何をやってるんですか？
What am I doing?
Why, spring cleaning, Kageyama-kun.
（神室）
何って大掃除だよ 影山君
Spring cleaning?
（律）
大掃除？
You said it yourself, didn't you?
（神室）
君が言ったんだろう？
"There is trash called
delinquents in our school.
“校内に不良と呼ばれる
ゴミどもがいる”
The student council should
get rid of them."
“生徒会で彼らを排除すべきだ”
I never said anything that extreme.
（律）
そんな過激なことは言ってない！
Please don't twist my words—
勝手に人の発言を
ねじ曲げないでくださ…
By the way, Kageyama-kun.
（神室）
ところで 影山君
This is the desk of our school's biggest
piece of trash, Onigawara-kun.
これは我が校の最も目立つゴミ
鬼瓦君の机なんだ
あっ 本気なんですか？ 会長
A-Are you serious, President?
Why would an elite like you...
エリート志向のあなたが
どうして？
An elite?
（神室）
エリート志向？
That's just an imaginary persona
that someone labeled me with.
そんなものは
他人にパッケージングされた
架空の人物にすぎない
You've realized it, too, haven't you?
君も気付いているんだろ？
That the praise others lavish upon you
doesn't actually fit who you really are.
周りからの評価は
自分の正体には向いていないことに
あっ…
Come, help me, Kageyama-kun.
（神室）
さあ 影山君も
またテストで
満点 取ったんだって？
You got another perfect score on your test?
I'm...
（律）
僕は…
律は僕より器用だし
変なことしないし
Ritsu is much more talented than I am
and doesn't do anything weird.
（徳川）
兄のマネは よせ
Don't try to act like your brother.
Even I...
（律）
僕だって…
Hey, do you think
I'll be able to do this, too?
僕にも できるようになるのかな？
Yeah.
（モブ）
うん！
だって 律は僕の弟だもん
Of course you will. You're my little brother.
Really? Yay!
（律）
そっか～ やった～！
Huh?
（女子生徒）
えっ？
（郷田）
フッ フッ フッ フッ フッ フッ…
All right, we made it to the goal.
よ～し ゴールだ
You've got some good muscles
on you, Onigawara.
なかなかいい筋をしてるぞ 鬼瓦
（鬼瓦）
ハア… チクショ～
Damn it... You called me out early,
早くに呼び出すから
so I thought you were going to tell me
who the shadow leader is!
ついに裏番の正体を明かすもんだと
思ったじゃねえか！
Remember that pain and how
good it feels, Onigawara.
そのつらさ そして気持ち良さを
覚えておけ 鬼瓦
The one you're looking for is
also fighting with himself.
お前が捜してる“彼”も
自分と戦っている
So you should change, too.
ならば お前も変わることだな
ハッ 上等！
Fine!
Bring it on!
やってやろうじゃねえか！
There's been an incident!
（男子生徒１）おい 事件だ 事件！
（男子生徒２）うわあ 気持ち悪い
Whoa, that's creepy!
（女子生徒たち）
早く何とかしてよ！
警察 呼んでよ！ 警察！
Hurry and do something about it!
Can the student council
do anything about it?
Call the police!
We're so grossed out, there's no way
we can take classes normally!
（女子生徒１）
このままじゃ キモすぎて
授業とか無理なんですけど！
Now, now, calm down.
まあまあ 落ち着いて
生徒会主導の下 犯人捜しをし
必ず突き止めてみせるから
I promise that the student council
will find the culprit and stop them.
鬼瓦の机は 君が開けるんだ
You open up Onigawara's desk.
We'll have to inspect everyone's belongings.
（神室）
まずは 手荷物検査をします
If they get caught like this,
they must be pretty stupid.
（男子生徒３）
これで見つかったら
よほどのバカだぜ
Oh, the teacher's not here yet?
おう！
先公は まだ来てねえのか
I was about to ruin my record
of never being late or absent.
（鬼瓦）
無遅刻無欠席記録が
止まるところだったぜ～
どうした？ 鬼瓦君
息が荒いね
What's the matter, Onigawara-kun?
You seem out of breath.
What's Kamuro doing here? What's going on?
（鬼瓦）
あん？
なぜ神室が ここに？
何だ？ この空気は
Did something happen?
何かあったのかよ？
I found them.
（律）
ありました
They were all in Onigawara-san's desk.
鬼瓦さんの机の中にありました
あ？ 誰だ？ てめえ
Who the hell are you?
Why are you going through my desk?
何 勝手に 他人の机…
So it was you, Onigawara-kun!
鬼瓦君 君だったのか！
は？ 何のこと…
Huh? What are you—
（女子生徒２）
変態
Pervert.
どいつだ？ 今 言ったの！
Who the hell just said that?!
何だよ？
What the heck?
What exactly did you find in my desk?
俺の机の中に何があったんだよ？
盗まれた女子たちのリコーダーが
君の机から発見されたんだよ
We found all of the girls' missing
recorder pieces in your desk.
人目を盗んで
ペロペロするつもりだったんだろ？
I'm sure you were going to lick
them when no one was looking...
You're such a pervert, Onigawara-kun.
変態の鬼瓦君！
What? Kamuro, don't make me punch you!
（鬼瓦）
あ？
神室 てめえ ぶん殴るぞ！
今なら まだ間に合う
謝るんだ！
There's still time! Apologize!
（鬼瓦）
うっ う…
マジで何だよ？ この空気
Seriously, what is this?
俺が そんなことする人間だと
思うかよ？
Do I really look like someone who'd do that?
君は他人に暴力を振るう人間だ
You are violent with other people.
信用を失うには それだけで足る
That's reason enough not to trust you.
W-Wait! It wasn't me!
まっ 待て！ 俺じゃねえ！
O-Oh, yeah! If I really wanted to lick them,
I would take them out of the school!
そ… そうだ！
隠れてペロペロが目的なら
学校から持ち出すだろ？
Only an idiot would leave them in his desk.
机にしまうなんて
バカのやることだぜ
Well, you're an idiot, aren't you?
だって 君はバカじゃないか
（鬼瓦）
う…
理不尽な理屈こいてんじゃねえぞ
神室～！
Stop being unreasonable, Kamuro!
There were some in his bag, too.
（律）
かばんの中にもありました
So you had taken a number of them home.
やはり 何本かは
持って帰っていたんですね
My school bag...
I left it wide open in my locker.
（鬼瓦）
俺の通学かばん
ロッカーに置きっ放しにしてた！
Kageyama-kun, you even put some in
his bag? You're all into this.
（神室）
影山君
かばんにも仕込んでたのか！
ノリノリじゃないか！
You bastard!
てめえ！
勝手に人のかばんを！
Stop snooping around my bag!
You're going to resort to violence?
（律）
暴力ですか？
（男子生徒）
放せよ！
Let him go!
You're taking it out on a first-year?
Poor Kageyama-kun!
（女子生徒たち）
影山君が かわいそうでしょ！
ヤバッ！
So gross.
So it wasn't Tenga the Demon,
but Tenga the Recorder Licker!
So violent!
消毒しなきゃ！
I have to disinfect mine.
Give us back our recorders!
You're terrible!
最悪！ この変態！
You pervert!
Pervert!
（生徒たち）
変態！ 変態！ 変態！ 変態！
変態！ 変態！
Pervert!
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Screw you all!
（鬼瓦）
ふざけんなあああ！
Run, everyone! The pervert's mad!
みんな 逃げろ！
変態が怒ったぞ
（女子生徒たち）
変態！ 変態！ 変態！ 変態！
気持ち悪い！ 気持ち悪い！
気持ち悪い！
No... No! I didn't do it!
（鬼瓦）
違う… 違う！ 俺は やってない！
Isn't... Isn't there someone
who'll take my side?
誰か… 誰か味方は いないのか？
I'll...
（マリコ）
私ね…
I'll marry you when I get older, Tenga-kun.
（マリコ）
おっきくなったら
天牙君と結婚するの！
D-Don't be stupid!
（鬼瓦）
バ… バカ言ってんじゃないやい
そうだよ マリコ
That's right... Mariko!
お前なら 俺を信じてく…
You believe me, don't you...?
（マリコ）
キモ…
Gross!
Gross
（鬼瓦）
どわっ！
うおっ！
ああ…
うわあ！
（女子生徒３）
きゃ～！
You're so gross, you perv!
汚らわしい この変態！
On this day, after two years of hard work,
（ナレーション）
この日 ２年以上をかけて
積み重ねてきた—
Onigawara Tenga's perfect
attendance record was broken.
鬼瓦天牙の無遅刻無欠席記録は
途絶えた
What's the matter?
（密裏）
どうした？
落ち込むことはない
Don't be down. Everyone has bad days.
スランプは誰にだってあるさ
Did you see, Kageyama-kun?
Onigawara's face...
（神室）
影山君 見た？ 鬼瓦の顔
The despair of not being able
to solve something by fighting!
得意のケンカじゃ
何ひとつ解決できない絶望
He's finished!
彼は もう終わりさ フフフ
（律）けっ！
（密裏）おお？
何をしてるんだ？ 僕は
What am I doing?
I'm going home.
（律）
帰ります
（密裏）
え？
Huh?
I actually don't have psychic powers.
（律）
実は僕 超能力ないので
またまた！ ちょっ…
Oh, come on... Hey, wait!
Kageyama-kun?!
影山君！
（霊幻）
おお！
モブの弟じゃねえか
If it isn't Mob's little brother.
I see you're giving me
the cold shoulder as usual.
相変わらず
俺にはトゲトゲしてんなあ
What are you wandering around
near my house for?
うちの近所で
何をうろついてるんです？
最近 この辺に出没する
不気味な幽霊の—
I got a request to exorcise a creepy ghost
that's been showing up in this area.
除霊依頼が入ったんでな
Want to help me out?
ついでに 手伝ってくれねえか？
（律）
お断りします
No. Unlike my brother,
I don't have any special powers.
兄と違い
僕に特別な能力はないので
Really? But you're Mob's little brother...
そうなのか？ モブの弟なのになあ
Why don't you exorcise this ghost yourself?
Aren't you a psychic?
（律）
あなたこそ 霊能力者だったら
自分で解決したらどうですか？
（霊幻）
ハハ…
Kageyama quit by throwing a spoon?
Not a towel?
影山が“さじを投げた”って？
フフフ
He's got quite the sense of humor.
意外とユーモアがあるんだなあ 彼
でも 俺が思うに
あいつは才能 薄いぜ
But as far as I can see,
he doesn't have much talent.
いや そいつは どうだろう？
Actually...
I'm not so sure about that.
Hm?
（律）
ん？ 何だ？ これ
Kageyama
What's that?
It's not... a balloon?
風船？
…じゃない
～
Ritsu continues to go wild
by pairing up with Dimple.
（霊幻）
エクボと組んで
明日なき暴走を繰り返す律
And then the gang leader alliance
makes its move.
そんな中 ついに動きだす
調味(ちょうみ)市番長連合
Meanwhile, some scary people
try to make Mob buy a vase.
一方 モブは怖い人に
つぼを買わされそうになる
Both brothers are in huge trouble!
兄弟そろって大ピンチだ
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 7:
次回「モブサイコ100」
第７話
“昂揚(こうよう)　喪失を手に入れた”
"Exaltation
~I've Obtained Loss~"
Exaltation
~I've Obtained Loss~
Illegal downloads?
You're going to be cursed.
違法ダウンロード？
あなた 呪われますよ！